Daniel Hurtado Cárdenas

Graduated in Computer Engineer

PERSONAL DETAILS

birth date August 21, 1978

address Pielago 3, 1° C, Ciudad Real, Spain

phone (+34) 600-382-692 e-mail dani@cianuro.net web page danicianuro.github.io

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Dynamic and used to working under pressure and in a team. Experience in customer service and great sense of responsibility. High dedication to service, able to generate added value to the organization by creating ideas and initiative to solve problems. I am an entrepeneur who likes challenges, self-taught by nature. I pay special attention to small details. I make friends easily and I never close doors to a difficulty. What I would highlight about the passion is the with which I do things.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ARCO research group

2014-2015

"Architecture and computer networks" - UCLM

- Beta tester.
- Making PCB's, user control, work order degree.
- Using MVC patterns, Observer design such as, Singleton and Agile.
- Design and implementation of communication and tracking servers.

UCLM 2011-2013

Computer centre and service

- Technical assistant.
- Windows Management Systems.
- Making user manuals.
- Helping users.
- Supercomputing services.

La Invencible

2005-2010

Performing arts studio

- Founding Partner, CEO.
- Over 500 functions performed.
- Festivals, events, performances, tours, productions in different continents.

Government of Mexico

2006

State of Chihuahua

- Technical director.
- Artists like Joaquin Cortes and Jose Carreras.
- International Festival of Chihuahua.

Cia.Nuro

2003-2007

Company of street theater and circus

- Technical director.
- Responsible of the sound, lighting, equipment, marketing and web design.
- Managing a group of 100 people.

LUPE

2003-2004

Image and sound

- Lighting technician.
 - Design, assembly and infrastructure control lighting.

EDUCATION

Graduated on Computer Engineer

2010-2015

University of Castilla-La Mancha

- Computer engineer.
- Parallel programming, embedded systems, network, security.
- Final graduation project: Drone Heal.

Superior cycle on computing and telecommunications

2000-2002

IES Torreón del Alcázar-Ciudad Real

• Making multimedia, network installation and antennas, programming.

Autonomous navigation for flying robots

2015

Technische universität München (German institute of science & technology - TUM) Design and development of system control of UAV's, 80 hours.

Course Drupal

2011

UCLM

Design and development of social networks, 80 hours.

Course of business management

2004

Trading center of Ciudad Real 500 hours.

Course of web page design

2003

CCOO-Ciudad Real

Design and development of web page, 300 hours.

Course of nanotechnology

2003

CCOO-Ciudad Real

Office suites and computer management, 150 hours.

Course of mounting networks

2003

UGT

Design and mounting networks, 200 hours.

Course of english

2000

England

Native teachers 500 hours.

SKILLS

Languages Spanish (native)

English (high).

Software Eclipse, NetBeans, CorelDraw, VegasPro, SoundForge, Django,

Latex, OpenMp, Bootstrap, Angular, CSS, Mercurial, Debian, Office tools, Solidworks, Autocad, Blender, Visual Studio, MPI,

Selenium, Vagrant, Android.

Soft lan-

guage

Python, C, C++, Matlab, PHP, Javascript, Java, Html, Ada.

REFERENCES

Delegate centre ESI-UCLM 2012-2014